yo yo periscope
periscoping yeah periscope yeah don't
hold it
people
no hands it's driving then you see the
rav4 has quite a serious torque limit
does no trouble with with turns unlike
some other cars where the other cars
outright on the speedloader behind 64
is not a limited so no don't Stefano
elevation so 75 up there which is our
max speed we're only going 64 because
the car in front of us
it works it works many people we got 42
rap for limited but the left we're limit
is on the edition of the call graph or
limit is that what this is yeah it is a
limit that they are asking limited we
bought like a platinum we bought the
highest trim yeah yeah they said he's an
interior looks like a limited right what
is nice really like that that's why you
got it tears nice
oh there's a
yeah that's that young Fed the retail
eons have better have a better family
the retail he loves a better fan
Italians have better fan it's nothing
worse than it's better than they you see
I know the retail eons are the
high-pitched whine is gone it's because
of noise about power line Georg dudes
why are you taking a self-driving car
awareness toward Las Vegas cuz it's not
all the way to Jersey you guys I got a
Vegas allow those niggas some time look
at this torch by the way serious torque
that's a real tour come for
now a self-driving car awareness - it's
really truly it's looking like the
Midwest we got some really cool about
slide up we'll get some press for them
we'll talk we're parently talking to
where classroom with fifth graders about
how you can achieve your dreams turn on
tune in drop out you know two-minute
drops right never too early Leary these
kids
now this Hill very nice that you can
just I mean we have to sit here places
to enforce exactly then you will make
some mistakes too which is the shittiest
part like it's not like you trusted to
not make mistakes it's zero guaranteed
DIY we are guaranteed the oh I
absolutely
it works pretty damn lucky haven't
really seen it like make mistake you
know it's been fine sweetie if I don't
do something yeah is the tour one way
the tour is one way yes the tour is one
way yes
she wears one why where's your first pop
song City Salt Lake City which table
when we go some do some ski to Winter
Park to George why do you hate Ford
fusions Oh God have you ever driven a
Ford fusions
I love these a crap move to the police I
police that was double paulie's huh how
many miles would have this engagement
well right now right now probably and
[Music]
they've been like minor things like a
mole frustrated let's slow this guy's
going that's not your fault
that's yeah but this current actually
we're gonna read you an open file to
excel like it should be accelerating a
little bit faster I feel right now you
can be a little bit more aggressive than
that see what is it six yeah
like kickball
what stop are you looking forward to the
most stop my looking forward to the most
I can see my friends in Chicago that's
always good it's not a real tour stop
we're gonna see a lots gonna shape up we
get some t-shirts made we would do like
that it's gonna be like the Warped Tour
it can be like the Warped or you know
just do you consider steering
Corrections just engagement oh yeah
so the only thing I've really had to do
was touch the wheel when that thing gets
low so I'm gonna touch the wheel right
now you haven't tested no pilot copilot
rav4 gravure have four and six five four
three no and a cure Lexus Toyota Priuses
Toyota Prius are now officially
supported however I think the rav4 and
Pacific is much nicer than embrace the
rav4 this car works particularly well
nobody's like a nice car too this is the
third most popular car in America for
what it is with the cost I understand
that's like 30k for a fully loaded one
it's nice right
replacing the minivans of the world yeah
yeah no one so many bad thing going
sport activity vehicles when is the
five-minute timer being removed never
right now the timer will be the timer
will be different probably in 0.4 or in
0.4 we'll roll out the new timer so the
new timer is going to be more based on
the confidence of the system at an
actual time it's also going to reward
you for responding quickly and punish
you for not responding quickly that's
fine though it wasn't there would have
been okay that's the thing I feel like a
lot of the when you actually have this
engagements there it's like they're
overly cautious there are you making the
decision abcess engage because i don't
want to see if this is going to work
yeah the way a lot of the way a lot of
the companies that reports as engagement
to the fourth loop is they only report
things they consider would have been
critical had I not disengaged yes like
when I'm urging lanes I'd rather
just do it well exactly like that if I
touch the wheel that's a failure of the
system right the system should do better
I'm not trying to build us we're not
trying to build a system that optimizes
for some like idea of what driving is
we're building a system that optimizes
for you having a better experience right
so if you felt at all unsafe that's
actually a failure of the system whether
it was unsafe or safe and reality
doesn't matter all about how you feel
we care about our consumers like
Calma hey I had what was this time you
comrade cares about feelings or
something how feelings matter feelings
matter bro that's what it was
any other questions and embarrassments
shownu's he said and center your cover
and I'll modify it for you to fit with
the draft oh yeah you can do that or did
we want this up here yeah so you can put
the cover back on you could like Dremel
out the thing someone did that I get to
look pretty good
please ask is he has new sensor
installed
Oh new sensor are you talking about the
pigeon they talking about the pigeon sir
the pigeon no this car doesn't have a
pigeon so it was gonna have a different
name but we actually really liked pigeon
too much so we're calling it the common
a pigeon what is it I'll tell you after
we're we haven't announced what the
pigeon is yet but we will announce that
the name is Pitt officially decided this
morning officially decided this morning
the name is pigeon pigeon however no
further details have been released on
the pigeon at this point they will say
it is gray like a pigeon we are driving
to Los Angeles from San Francisco for
nibs guys and how many aeons will ship
in the first batch like the first batch
the the first two batches are gonna ship
really close to each other but we have
ten Aeons made in the basement right now
we have six sounds made for us this
actually isn't even a retailer yawn and
they asked if we wanted to stretch it
out
this is development version yeah
development you agree they're almost the
same the fan circuit was cleaned up a
little George would you ever give Trump
a ride
that sounds intimidating man that sounds
intimidating no he does not have his
hands on the wheel keeping hands little
wheel all times gross evil lurk of the
wheel now you gotta pay attention at all
times I'm actually but your hands on the
wheel if it messes up as long as you're
paying attention you have plenty of time
to reach out grab
went on saw three-point-nine release
coming
Oh also soon TM maybe maybe maybe today
no no don't ask controls team oh that's
much sooner than most people soon Oh
three point zero point three point nine
is very soon okay
yeah zero point four look but Chiffre
plus zero point four is going to ship
before open pilot zero point four
what do you think of the Neo driven guys
big fans
those wasn't right that made that Oh
Tessa guy yeah he built videos you would
sell them back before coming I saw the
owns do you use the factory lean keep
assess display for radar yes
so you see that there's a car visible
and that means that there's a car in
front of me which there is
two minutes left can really see the
timer
yeah Oh so yeah the downside I think I
said the bad news was everybody but no
new model model team is not doing so
great but model team might have some new
incredible stuff and then actually
announce with all the stuff is intense
just do it yeah it'll be kind of funny
you know if it actually comes out like
there's like ten papers talking about
what I figured out yesterday in like six
months it's actually it was first at its
george hotz moon what about the fall
just in spot another people yeah
father's this is stupid don't have that
that's stupid it doesn't maybe we'll
like repurpose it for like Siri coming
up on the or whatever we use - Siri what
well it will include all accent we want
to include one of those like voice
assistants make it better I think the
Google one is pretty good right what
supposed to be the best liar
I don't like my life so she's not that
smart
what are you doing in LA George go to
nips
go on and it's worth nip stand for
neural information processing systems
lips it's better than like I Clark
or CDP are you guys are pretty
conference aims all like you like weird
foil other things it's actually makes
the most sense we don't name our things
like block chain watch a watch Jane are
checking like comma a I invest
conference like the consensus in those
deaths just curious wondering it
conflict with rav4s built at Lehman
blame changes now you're rid of
George what you take on Bitcoin it's
made me a lot of money you know are you
speaking in them sorry god that's
beginners
did you ever fully flash the ECU on the
rav4 for full dynamic cruise no no
unfortunately below 20 below 20 it won't
accelerate they'll break all the way
down to zero which is la fed up the
scoring system oh yeah the other stocks
you don't the stock system does it just
disengages and will smash you into the
car in front so it'll just roll you at
20 miles an hour and so far zone yeah
that's worth the high quality right
that's very small but no we break all
the way down to zero this is 2017 right
20 step 2017 rav4 limited rav4 Limited
any update on Acura TLX support
No and you can do it will you flash my
civic ApS on tour no no no no no Tour
green flashes Oh
enjoy your stock torque be happy with
that learn to appreciate your stock
torque stock fork man or buy a Toyota
and your fake it'll hump or torque look
at this look at that torque bro that's a
real torque really there how long before
nine lane keep assist features like
stopping at red lights
I heard red light for scams no no no no
no red lights it back on the agenda oh
yeah when the pigeon launches yeah uh
okay
the pigeons gonna let you stop at red
lights the pigeon will let you stop yeah
oh why we're all the party in San Jose
oh oh let go oh yeah that'll let go
somewhere hold on yes we're nearly great
if open pilot came with weighs 0.40
am I taking 87 is the only question
I'm not gonna take one a wonderful wire
yeah we take it like that like thing
where it like cuts across you know I'm
talking about
you know you don't like that little
sketchy thing looks like yeah no no but
to get to five there's like some like
it's like it's like a like a subway on
it you know no this is you're just gonna
stay you know say on CA one one get to
do to get to them yeah look it stopped
detecting that laymen's abbas docile
week which one should be detected
nothing the monster doesn't like don't
worry the new revolutionary machine
learning system will fix this the
revolution and bro autopilot is on bro
autopilot on bro
wait why do why do you think this is a
joke he's not driving though there's a
guy in the back with an Xbox controller
on the back show movies actually no guy
actually no guy we have some you on most
cardboard cutouts on the way back there
that we can hear the Aeon fan with the
headphone on the periscope does that
business is the spam feed variable
yeah the fan speed is variable the
retail edition is better about it we can
also change the policy a little bit the
policy is a little you only hear it when
it's out like its highest level and it's
well the pigeon also do stop signs yes
yeah the pigeon will not go from stop
something stuff so basically it's gonna
stop and then you're gonna have to tell
it when it's safe to go okay that's fair
yeah because detecting whose turn is to
go in a stop sign is actually well also
there's actually I but at red lights
when they turn green it'll go
automatically yes because that's much
more so than some guy thinking it's his
turn to go exam have to stop talking
with you can yeah so yeah can you
straight on 101 prefer for 2018 Los
Angeles Los Angeles well we got a ways
to go over that was driving wouldn't it
be nice yeah nothing like it sketchy but
I just my concern level just one up five
points
yeah you know we'll be nice now if a
pilot like known about Oh
your cousin iPhone annex there goes that
phone it would have been nice is if open
pilot like knew about this and like get
it early on for us like it could
you know when will you sell sensors
between lane changes when will we sell
pigeons locations are only free whoa -
big talk to big torque
- big dork this is this is a lot of
torque right now this is a lot of torque
we're going fast around the sharp curve
so that's beyond the torque that they
have even the Toyota someone saw your
speed on the thing when you Florida only
cuz I was going too fast once they saw
my speed I was I going fast you say
cruising at 90 I'm gonna get some
traffic up here let's hope we don't fall
below 20 because if we do fall below 20
open pile is gonna disengage but we're
40 so all right someone asked where is
Biff his bad visit home easy huh yeah
how do I do it
wow that's a lot of lights um Viv's at
home yeah
and I go faster go fast scrolls columns
Co I really help 156 know bird I don't
want to want to throw in her feet we're
in there and then you're gonna stay on
here until you were John to 152 or
whatever yeah you have 28 files on here
does the system detect detect objects in
the middle of the road yes yes
you won't alert you it'll stop feeling
it it'll stop do not yell if it's a car
yeah yeah what's bibs relationship to
the company she's VP of Operations right
visit home shipping your Aeons while we
sit in the car for six only five and a
half hours know what's going down yeah
would you share what would you share the
STL for the e on GoPro support for a
custom windshield angle yeah we can do
that what angle do you want
so the Aeons gonna include 20 degrees
and 28 degrees and then calibration is
good to plus or minus 4 degrees so that
actually gets you all the way from like
16 to 32 which is a big set of
windshield angles
um but if you really want something
outside of that right like like luckily
look at this calibrates right I can
stare the Box move down you can handle 4
degrees of calibration just the camera
alone
what year will the car drive itself goes
to coast well I mean it's gonna be 99%
no television no car awareness to her at
sad today at least on the highway we've
been 99% autonomous we have enough
drivers on the phones right now we're
not going coast to coast of Alaska
that's at the hello though la once we
get on five it really like well what you
got a five you can really forget about
you don't have to take any exits or you
know stock blind spot indicators yeah
their stock I don't know we should tell
controls team to do that ah that's the
controls he needs to do if controls team
controls team if you're watching I'd
love to know if we can actually get
access to those side radars then we can
have some auto lane tation right
Alexa change left yeah that's cool all
right
I like Saturn me lot Alexa take exit it
before we're going too slow
I do love these white spots temptress
out
like they make driving a lot nicer even
the stock ones Toyota it didn't okay job
number one once a lane change they even
said pretty please George oh pretty
please please please pretty please
lane changes after red lights and stop
signs after pigeons eat pigeons did you
get a no win lane change is possible
all right because the blind spot
detector is actually not enough right
you have to know if there's a lane there
that you can change into that is true
when his own alligator ship elects a boy
service soon now that's a 0.4 feature
like 0.4 is gonna be a lot of those
features
the truth is red light will stop signs
may not fully work until 0.5 you'll
start seeing beta support for than 0.4
what was pigeons original discovery of
those pants on
zone live well I can't talk about what
the original name was because it gives
away what it is but the good thing about
it being pidgin it's just like who knows
what a kitchen this man you just gonna
have a zoo of animals yeah I'm gonna
ready in the shop to the zoo my bad idea
go to the zoo zoo bro I paid their draft
you know if you think about a pigeon
it's actually a piggy on someone said
latest open pilot is so good at just
reset during the car when it's in half
the lane isn't that very close to lane
changing oh yeah yeah you can do yeah
that's always been you can do half my
judge oh so what if you just get into
the lane it already center itself yeah
you're saying there's like just push it
over here and I'll let go
whoo yeah that's a partial lane change I
mean that's that's what what Tesla does
right now right so no Tesla you actually
turned the blinker on an auto lane
changes but that doesn't work I've tried
without without turning the wheel at
work point but there's a few major
problems with Tesla's doing first off
they don't have to side radars they're
using ultrasonics don't use ultrasonic
sprawl ultrasonics are terrible
um the other problem yeah like I get
sketched out in places like that the car
drove totally flies I know I well the
thing is honestly I'm not afraid of the
car goes we're all afraid of the guy
yeah maybe that's the beach threat with
driving a car is a bullying look at like
I'm like why are we slowing down so much
because you have that look that thing is
slowing down right you don't see it the
radar is superhuman oh that truck is
slowing down
yeah yeah right that trucks going mad
slow takeover
we'll see so yeah we when we tracked his
engagements we track what was done for
the disengagement so there's four kinds
of disengagement right there's gas brake
steering and can't
so dis engagements with the gas are
considered not safe differently because
in general if you want to give it more
gas than open I was giving it it
probably wasn't doing something unsafe
that probably just was pissing me walk
yes brake disengagement SAR the worst
ones yes you're just engaged with the
brake okay that means something went
wrong does that mean something went
wrong and steering dis engagements are
not great either particularly sharp
steering disappearance so we pay most
attention to those but ya know 2018 is
just gonna be a race to drive down this
engagement ride over again last and last
and less and less until they were so few
and our hardware is so reliable that we
can make it level 3 yeah
wait when do the levels change I've
noticed this no you're like five and
yeah yeah yeah no like when you
like first started , it was what you
were level three you need it to get to
level four right and now it's like
you're level two and you did level three
the the levels change what is this
last two numbers in it really changed it
just kind of became legally advantageous
to always only calling yourself level 2
okay how much curious because that was a
level 5
right well I lost little five was always
level four which is fully its bullet
okay so the distinction between five and
four is four means it's fully autonomous
on certain routes five means it's fully
autonomous everywhere cars control
yes so you can have a level four car but
it's just limited in the places it can
take you a level five or my particular
that's the distinction so someone wants
to know if you removed the the message
telling you to regain the wheel in this
car no no I don't know if they just saw
it and they said yeah absolutely not and
don't do that
don't remove the message that's bad yes
six minute timeout is still absolutely
functional we don't take it out it's a
good safety feature Oh
as far as the one that talks about the
torque limit I mean then comes up much
less likely on the Toyota the Honda
because the Toyota has much higher
torque the one that says like you know
sorry that turns to sharp yeah turns are
just way more likely to be too sharp on
the
what are we kind of nice I haven't
driven a lion to eat is over by like
that's right I got pulled over once
those bottles for doing wanna speeding
95 that's bad to know in 74 we're good
no like when it flashes Ward and demands
you to hold the wheel every 20-30
seconds yes we're talking about no it
was never removed and it's not open I
never demanded that you hold the wheel
over 20 seconds
no it demands every six minutes that you
touch the wheel to prove that you're
still there yeah exactly those things
are not those things are not good like
like so there's a difference between an
actual safety and liability right so you
think about that thing we're like Toyota
will like disengage at 20 miles an hour
and just like let you slam into the car
in front of you right yeah that clearly
was done for liability reasons if not
for safety reasons yes and if that's the
distinction I will always favor actual
safety over liability Lagos just which
manufacturers is this neon currently
compatible with what cars are so
remember that the EON is a dashcam you
have to modify it if you want to work as
a self-driving unit the Aeons we sell
cannot drive leanness you have to modify
and we don't publish instructions about
how to modify it you're on your own
finish such as so everyone knows eons
are a general purpose - game general
purpose a dash cam developing kit not a
self-driving car you can modify them and
do whatever you guys with whatever you
please might be such a hypocrite my time
to control yeah he promises you won't
see you like so that's right that's
right don't get you won't get sued do
whatever you would like with the exactly
you buy in a store but yeah so so open
pilot is compatible with there's a list
of supported cars on the website it's
hot as a Toyotas and that girl no okay
right the same car Lexus and Toyota is
in the same car
just a badging scam it's actually quite
we're in the middle lower you're always
better off buying a high trim of the
cheaper brand and a low trim of the more
expensive grant a lot of people don't
know this they don't know what I think
I'm gonna touch us again I'm just to
reset the thing so masters I like we
have a Honda Civic touring and we have
like a base-model dialect the Honda
Civic Touring is a much nicer car
you're better off buying a high trim of
the cheaper brand then a low trim of the
luxury brand mmm like a low trim Lexus
is a worse car than a high trim Toyota
obvious light trim Lexus better than hi
to figure out of it they charge you more
for a low trim lexus than a hydro to the
other and the hydro period is better car
they're built like largely on the same
platform
I'm like the aisle accidents have a code
of same car the same car let's say
platform now there's lots in court well
now there's a few because a few changes
made to it but like it's the same
platforms and Jesse's it's actually even
worse turn the I Alexa yeah like so we
have us at 9th gen Civic in the 9th gen
Civic bad reviews really Pacific where
is tension tamers much better
do they still think it's a trick no
there was there's one guy thought it was
trailer guy thought it was a chick
there's a white guy thought it was a
trick we're faking self-drive you're
actually driving any me over there
it's as real as it gets
we'll open pilot disengage if another
driver merges into your lane and if you
get rear-ended ouchie that's a good
question will it a notice if somebody
make you and stop the car
yeah no hey wall huh can't you do that
in there crash bar over our that you can
tap into or something
like when the crash bars hits off the
car no actually it will it will open
pilot will disengage if like ya know it
will and actually well if all the pilot
detects like a set of faults with the
car it will disengage okay so um yeah
that would be that would be considered a
fault backseat driving is illegal and we
will not do that for example a if the
air bags go off yeah definitely
okay if you just gently lightly tapped
No
can you explain what the upside down
with the Honda Odyssey
oh so the Honda Odyssey the connector up
here is literally upside down from the
Civic so when you try to plug the
giraffe in it plugs in upside down and
it doesn't fit really yeah
that's he apologizes how
difficult is it in your opinion to get
open pilot to work with other cars it
depends on who you are depends on who
you are and what car how difficult would
it be to get to work with like a Toyota
Camry not hard at all how difficult
would be to got to work with a Ford
Fusion disgusting because you have to
sit inside a Ford Fusion I'm still
waiting for somebody to pour this over
to a luxury exotic car I'm waiting for
the first open pilot rolls-royce make
you a deal if you buy me a Maybach or
rolls-royce ghost I will pour it to that
car you hear that you have if you have a
Maybach or rolls-royce ghost I will
personally do it separate from comma buy
one for me growls right back he will
attempt to get your rolls-royce Silver
Bay back this all drop that's right no I
totally will man love one of those cars
someone's got to have the crypto gains
to do that this year
right someone's gotta buy me a little
bored
got to get rolls-royce to do it sponsor
you you know about when you thought you
were gonna get a rolls-royce and then
you do it's really absurd so you know
about um what was it gah
crystal or Dark Crystal right the guy
who made Cristal the guy who made
Cristal was once being interviewed um
and like Walt you know upstanding Kyle
French guy you know very very well
dressed he's like I don't really like
the way if it be on a certain
demographic of rappers and people who
aren't members of upper society are
using our product you know we were just
rather they didn't buy it
Christophe went from being the top
selling luxury champagne to light below
like really
jay-z called for an absolute ban on
Christoph this guy nobody if I see
you treated crystal that's so not cool
and completely plummeted um yeah and
then Dom prignon became a thing does
the doctor joke I was like we love
anyone who buys our every great man I'm
soft
I feel like Rolls Royce is a similar way
like Rolls Royce expects like the stuffy
British executive to buy a Rolls Royce
yes and it's actually like post below
yes expect like the Exxon CEO
are we close to somewhere wait where's
my phone there it is
did I miss the exit no I don't know
tap for George know your point I would
like to point out that plenty of miles
to get to 180 time for the plug is the
issue for the Honda Odyssey Howard the
other car mechanic connector of
diagnosis diagnosis no it's not the pan
of plug giraffe giraffe is a lot of hand
grandpa pants fit in all cars you know
how hard we worked to make pandas tiny
really hard and as a Chinese they fit
everywhere they're banned out there yes
there's no fan up there we're dry right
now on a panda panda panda panda all
right yo George what was the ML Legend
tweet about haha
yo guys if that works you have no
idea how good oh yeah revolution which
car model does okapi work best him
a porcelain it depends there's some
advantages specific and some advantages
to the rav4 I think in the long run
I bet on the rav4 grab for you heard it
first 2017 rav4 limited beautiful cards
at 33 ounces it is a beautiful car
because we're much more likely to ship
the reflash that fixes the 20 mile an
hour thing than to ship a reflash the
fix of the tour much safer when you're
reflashing the engine it's much safer
than reflashing is what's the worst an
engine bust accelerate step on the brake
what's the worst the steering does the
experience as well d the accelerations
have to be I know my safe
there is more of a problem in the truck
all of them so I said you can have a
GoFundMe campaign for the different
models but you have about the system we
have bounty it's not even a gofund means
we pay you if you do the pork if you do
the pork come to come little baby 10k
like those cars all right you gotta
office treatment so since I'm remember a
little more than that guy well yeah I
mean here's the cool thing
why don't you set up whoever you aren't
brokest it ever go fund me a your car
supporter go set up a go fund come set
up a go fund me get someone to do it
like a pilot open-source go contact the
guys like github that are ported
previous cars right there's two of them
there in the pleura cross section
mr Hayden like I hate to give his even
when I'm I hate trucks as well when I'm
driving to our fire
would also work on the rav4 hybrid
should
what is this it's a carnival
Wow is it kind of looks like a carnival
no it's a farmers market Christmas trees
there's some kind of adapter the
draftees look at the pillars of the
website slash buy one that really should
be zoo dock a little airport just like
the Gilroy Airport or something
[Music]
and some white whales
that's God Jesus lifts when are we gonna
work on those lifted f-150s one-minute
Lincoln ever plays on mobile I hate you
wanted the Tesla Model S pull request
right now pretty soon actually that
thank you would probably be really easy
to really yeah that's probably better
view is never expected yeah no that one
that was on the bad people are excited
about the Tesla Ford's the cars that
people are excited about our Tesla's and
Chevy Volts but here's the thing nobody
owns either one of those cars
Jim sold like seven Chevy Volts someone
said I have a feeling we're not gonna
see many Audi's no folks most popular
car manufacturer in Europe so if folks
might now do the same
somebody else might be working on those
but you know how much faith I have never
actually what the how do you guys yeah
but uh how much do you absolutely hate
the factory to have oh I don't bro do
you think we use the factory in haven't
never even used them we've never used it
how about you has these factory NAB's
this isn't that bad of a factory now no
I think yours was different from mine
but it was horrible of my pens what I
liked but really what I want is ways
right here and that's come out really
soon is open loud only supported in the
u.s. those open source it's like what do
you think of Alex Roy is the bro balance
sort of problem and we love to as the
bro he came to the Christmas party last
year
yeah he asked if he could be a partner
for self-driving car Awareness Week
absolutely Alex Roy I'm looking for
partners for soft rented car Awareness
Week many of you would like to thank
interfere we want to make people aware
that this is possible today sorry good
driving across the country who driving
across the enjoy everybody to show
people be aware like this works Toyota
if you work for Toyota understand how
you're not like yourself right
now look at this this is the Toyota this
is a Toyota we've been talking for an
hour and a half that we put on a
cellphone and a panda and that's really
what this is
well no that's what the is in a
very low alcohol a cellphone a panda of
course and lots of very complex software
is literally running Android right now
that's Android hope we don't get like a
text message you know as Amber Alert the
umbrella used to crash open pilot don't
worry
downtown is that the name of the town
you have two miles
any more resources for reversing canvas
of a panda and slash Cabana
I need dish no resources you can watch
it once on a periscope I have like a
medium post about it going slack the
inviters fixed I'm nobody's slave but to
get the high respect go to slack dock
amadhatter I you'll find good people
there Oh
they're right up the ass truck and we'll
do a little bit of periscoping on this
road it's a little bit different then
we'll turn the tires go off right there
mr. got people yes somebody's calling me
from San Francisco
choice Pam thank people get 56 I'll get
more
you've had 670 total love those viewer
numbers
wish I had this funeral my way if you're
bored mr. plugging for my soundcloud on
all periscopes soundcloud.com slash mom
remove a new music recently that's Cruz
with two zeros see R 0 0 se I was
inspired by James Dean you know the porn
star with the two V's I was like I'm
gonna be Tom Cruise with two O's and my
roommate was like nah man
one two albums with two zeros I got a do
an album one of these days Tom Cruise
with two zeros and his name was goose
with two zeros
yeah we should get you on a future with
little Windex an actual robbery like
what witness will fly you to has to have
to do a future yeah you should do a
future with little Windex so like check
out that torque let's slow down and see
we can even do this okay now you're
going no go right go right
sorry what no what laughs laughter
laughs that's what I thought
nice navigation flopped I got a
voicemail
oh it's gusto don't call me boys
custom calling because they try to
upsell you the payroll service
oh you have your number in there for
that oh yeah they could hi Thomas just
like to let you know if you'd like to
you know upgrade your control provider
so what the payroll platinum no no you
get him to do like your health insurance
and they do all the other stuff for you
then what would I use benefits for you
zenefits yeah we don't use other folks
myself
you give them health insurance I mean I
deal with oh great yo we should buy a
sandblaster yeah well we got to figure
out how to make it neon heatsinks look
nice
[Music]
hello quickness so you're going yeah
you're saying like free woman
please answer why did the manufacturer
made the connection that the draft goes
in why did the manufacturer make it yes
because that's what manufacturers do
manufacturers suck yeah okay so this
you're gonna see look so now I'm going
to me gasp quarter tang
we should stop eventually I got I just
don't know where the next gas station is
there's this stuff on the truck
okay it was like a Best Buy yeah yes I
didn't know if we get POW we're below 20
so I have to resume driving manually if
you saw that warning what is used from
it what is use from what I'm assuming
he's referencing the connection and Oh
like radars and no guys leak this
is all documented on the Internet
George have you not learned by now that
people don't like looking things up I'd
much prefer to come into a periscope and
ask that's the only skill that you need
to have in life okay look at that
serious Toyota torque right look at that
said it couldn't do that
so the can't turn
sure stop there for gas pretty good
price
[Music]
how long before rideshare uses common AI
without driver soon sure use Connie I
with driver whoa some some people now
I've heard I've heard from people like
yo man like like people reach out to us
like yo I was in an uber and they have
this thing that was driving they said it
was made by common AI really becoming I
well that I wonder if we would ban you
for doing that as an uber driver if did
not out they guess I'll cut your
contracting for a reason of course they
can you know about those people who are
like having people fill out surveys in
the back of the UV is saving money yeah
who ever tried to ban those and like
they weren't allowed to yeah I mean I
guess I don't know when it comes to the
safety of driving they have some more
control unsafe back it'd be questionable
if uber could that's interesting maybe
it certainly have like requirements on
the car I don't know well that's such a
good idea that for filling out surveys
for a free ride at the back seat well
they do that yeah I know guys like fill
out the survey don't stop you're right
five minutes yes exactly
he makes six dollars because you thought
the lots of survey yeah that's a great
idea
yeah
we is that Sonic the fast-food place
that exists out lost i thought sonic was
east coast only oh it is it's sonic
burger is damn
[Music]
so like this road and stuff is good for
open pilot unfortunately this car can't
do stop and go which is super
frustrating about oh you were talking
about a subway store you feel like
subway yeah and three people in the
channel we're like what the what do
you mean I recognize this one subway in
the middle of nowhere and I remember
then use that as a reference point daily
we stop there every time usually like
you know with someone of the curves
gotta get out of this car
ooh that drug
feel the power of the Rav
go-go-go-go opinion on caps Nets Nets
it's a net that takes your letters in
and puts them in cap cap also eight so
it's like when you do text-decoration
uppercase in CSS or one but that's right
the text transform uppercase to behave
like text decorate half soul networks Oh
cat so Jeff Hinton's thing oh I don't
know to be honest I haven't seen the new
stuff I saw the early stuff on capsule
networks like here's the thing you have
to realize about Jeff engine all right
like the man is an absolute genius and
invented a lot of great stuff but like
everyone who's invented a lot of great
stuff they've also invented a lot of
crap
nope so I don't know I mean I'm not
really a believer in it how am I
thinking this idea of like like extract
things I have to read the new stuff to
really get like a fair thing but when I
first saw and I'm like no this just
looks like like you're still believing
in features right not only do I not
believe in feature engineering I don't
even really believe in features like
sorry what's the future I don't know
it's just like this 512 dimensional
vector space look at this open pilot
look at that boy over pilot however it
did all the way up to here on this one
thing I did that's good now it's just
the problem was there were two double
yellow is you see the two W yes it was
confusing it it was locking on to the
other double yellow Oh add the center
prize yeah like now it's good so that
was that was a model failure
where the hell are doing your goai
traveling across the farm country
no hands
this is easy yeah this is you're not
gonna get much easier driving the mat it
was pretty nice roads are well painted
unlike most of California yeah that's
true okay these houses actually kind of
fun to live out here I think no I don't
think you can get like anything a me an
Amazon Prime
it was our friends everywhere I was on
prime yes yes some guy was like writing
about how he like lives on an island and
Amazon Prime delivers to him up look at
that we got a forward collision warning
amazing
well not was stupid though but you
didn't get forward collision no it said
brake risk of collision and it beeped
three times collision warning but it was
while the system was on and it braked
fine interesting so there was no actual
risk of collision whose fault is that
who's the Ford wind warning team no
feature engineering foam I mean that
wasn't like the worst false positive
like they're really annoying false
positives for fraud collisions
we get above 20 it can like make this
time we have to be above 20 because it's
stupid around 4
avocados three for a dollar I'm pretty
sure Whole Foods charges like six
dollars for a avocado
yeah well new Whole Foods is gonna lower
the prices because they're owned by
Amazon you know Amazon strategy for
lower prices zamboula doesn't believe in
making problem which is great i lose
greatest charity never exist they are I
don't know where I'd be without some of
the toys are for grandmas you're gonna
take that yo-yo this is a fast life we
are on a crash course what you think I
rap for it what's your rap I mean
look there's a lot of them yeah
regardless of what demographic it cars
for there's a lot of them on the road I
mean you know that's always the question
like are there more English teachers or
truck drivers that list Shakespeare as
their favorite author
truck drivers probably like like uh you
know who's that chick really no no but
the truth is just so many more truck
drivers that like you know you're just
better off going with that so that's why
we choose these cars personally no I
would not choose to drive around for but
if we drive the company cars the company
pays for gas which is which that's yeah
however I do have to say this is not bad
for a like non nice car that I chose the
second ride it is is very good very
other like really nice thing is this car
has open pilot which is super nice
yellow it is very nice I would much
rather take a rav4 that would let me not
have to actually draw have the entire
time versus driving like a nice person
you know like honestly when I had my
Mercedes I would get so mad that I
didn't have open handling drive what is
this that car didn't even have
adaptive cruise
like driving with so much effort driving
a lot about her driving is a lot of
effort
drive it
like this is like it's it's doing the
giraffe connected to the ER no this is a
panda right now the giraffe is connected
to the panda which is connected to the
e/m yeah
all right yes that's open paya today on
perhap for oh you know yawns do not come
with open pilot you have to modify your
yawn you have to do yourself
we can't help you with that we just
released open source software and
instead over some hardware yeah yeah we
should leave the periscope yeah work it
we're getting out an hour definitely any
final questions fashion speak now or
forever hold your peace
cuz he'll never periscope or down power
no one ever last one now let's go from
tips maybe well walk around nips and
make fun oh yeah if I have a vote
without driver assistant / radar is it
possible to retrofit for the Aeon
driving America wait really
someone just said driving should
buy it we should buy that dude one
little pigeon be released we don't know
yeah no no soon TM
yeah well ask any go everybody everybody
to end it and he tweeted any right now
but now to have Ewell's any Samuels
when's the pigeon coming out bro
everybody turn right there
everybody Samuels tell them you really
want the pill start working on it
no other questions all right later bro
later guys
[Music]